<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Home</title>
    <link>https://addds03.github.io/Addy-Portfolio/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://addds03.github.io/Addy-Portfolio/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Customer Analytics: _In Progress_</title>
      <link>https://addds03.github.io/Addy-Portfolio/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addds03.github.io/Addy-Portfolio/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>Data fragmented into 4 Segments using a combination of Principal Component Analysis (4 Components) and K-Means Clustering.  Career-focused - Young group of high-income and well-qualified people. Well-off - Mid-Age wealthy group in a big city. Standard - Average Population. (Middle Class) Few opportunities - Customers from small cities with mediocre income and not highly qualified.   A Descriptive Analysis of the Number of purchases, Brand choice, and Revenue generated per segment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toronto House Prices: A Hedonic Geospatial Analysis</title>
      <link>https://addds03.github.io/Addy-Portfolio/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addds03.github.io/Addy-Portfolio/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>Created a tool that estimates house prices (RMSLE ~ 0.1325) to help house buyers, sellers, or agent negotiate their house prices. Gathered data from multiple data sources, primary Zoocasa.ca, and external factors Toronto Open Data Portal, Airbnb.ca, Toronto Police Service Data Portal. Engineered 15 features from 8 different datasets using Python. Implemented geospatial proximity joins using K-dimensional tree package from &amp;lsquo;scipy&amp;rsquo; to engineer features on shapefile. Used Hedonic Spatial Regression to determine elastic 10% increase of features on the final price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Help Dognition Improve Test Completion of the Users.</title>
      <link>https://addds03.github.io/Addy-Portfolio/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://addds03.github.io/Addy-Portfolio/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>Area Customed advertising: Advertise in the area which has less number of test completion rate. Keeping in mind the areas with higher completion rates are not ignored completely. Timely Reminders: As we had seen that users are most active between 6-8 pm, set reminders for completing tests during the mentioned time and while the games where we have seen most drop-off periods. Use Social Media Marketing: As we can see that the &amp;lsquo;free start&amp;rsquo; trials by the company failed, users were still dropping out of the tests in between.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
